I look up to the stars And reach for
the sky I believe in tomorrow if we try,
I... Hey!
C'mon, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
C'mon, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one dream.
C'mon, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the good times.
We share the good times.
And maybe, maybe, oh,
we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see, but to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought on by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand out.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top, we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way.
I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts.
So don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood.
I feel so good.
I will be free to be.
Oh yeah.
Share the music.
Even if I.
Share the one dream.
I know where you are.
Share the good times.
Show us that smile.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Or we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Or we share the one world.
Wait a second!
What's going on?
Somebody help me! Look at that.
There's a lot more of
these guys than I expected
Man, you guys sure have some weird powers!
That rubber crap you do is way weirder!
You think so?
I don't believe it.
The mortars didn't have
an effect on any of them.
Yeah, these guys really
live up to their reputation.
This is no time to be impressed.
It's our job to hold these bastards
off until the Admiral arrives.
It's like we're going to wait that long.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't throw me!
Who the heck are you talking?
I don't really know, but my
body feels hot for some reason.
Body?
What are you talking about?
There's a headless body
running around on fire.
Help!
I'm burning up and it hurts!
But how can you even feel it?
Someone pour some water on it!
Hurry!
I thought I was a goner.
Listen, everybody, be careful!
That guy makes weird circles!
Don't get caught inside them!
Now, room.
So do you mean like this
that's right exactly like this?
Make yourselves comfortable this
will be over before you know it!
Start running this is the arm of a giant
and your ground don't even blink men just a
And fire at will, but Brigadier General,
sir, our weapons, they're,
they're flying away!
What the hell?
Look at that.
How did he do that?
There's no time to be impressed.
What? No way!
Hey! Those are my legs!
Give them back!
Where did my arms go?
You have too many chairs.
I know. All right.
Giant pistol.
This.
Oh, great.
It's already come to this.
What a sight.
And I don't even have eyes.
Captain's lost it. No surprise.
these rookies are quite reliable
indeed awful impatient aren't they
what's up with your body Straw Hat
not a cool finish doesn't matter
what they do their formations
don't amount to crap now Brigadier
General it appears the remaining
pirates have exit of the auction
house sir
they
want to escape
i won't let them make a mockery
out of us we've got plenty of
reinforcement the three hostages are
accounted for and secured at the
back entrance sir aim the motors
at the crew members without powers
firing squads to the rear we
are now commencing an Alto
attack move in now take them down
you see they've broken rank and
they're totally disorganized
they're running in for a blind
attack I'm back to normal
hey Straw Hats I'm glad I had
this little chance to meet
you but next time I won't
show you any mercy understand
Fair enough, but I'm the one
who's gonna find the One Piece.
Hey, Captain!
What are you standing around for?
Killer.
You know what?
On our journey up to this point,
we've been ridiculed whenever
we mention the One Piece.
They said we were on a fool's
errand searching for it.
And each time that happened, I
slaughtered everyone who even snickered.
What lies ahead is a sea
of death for those who
think the One Piece is
something to laugh at.
Let's meet again in the new world.
Move out, men!
Yes, sir!
Come on, go long!
How dare you treat us like
a bunch of toys! Mepo?
I want no gas!
Hey, Captain, are you
going back inside already?
Thanks, Sanji.
Hey, Luffy, look over there.
Here we are.
I'm this guy. What?
Did you call me handsome?
Anyway, we're all set to help
you guys get out of here.
Okay, are you ready to do this, Matt?
Yes.
Life is rosy and beautiful.
Wasn't really looking for help
from those goofballs again,
but I guess we're in a hurry, so...
Whatever, it'll be fun!
If you say so. Lullaby.
Escape while you can,
you two! Run! You got it!
Stop sleeping, dammit!
Hey, are you with those pirates?
No, not us, mister. We ain't pirates.
Pirates will scare us!
Knife fleur!
What the heck? With a twist.
Whoa that that was scary.
Poor head he suffered so much trauma
after navy headquarters hunted him down.
Get here doors what an amazing guy
quiet you two this is no time to
talk about trauma or anything else
we owe the young master our lives
we have to help him and his friends
out of this trouble Franky let's
move it right much obliged come
on don't let him escape after him
Holy crap how many of
these guys are there this
is certainly exciting I
like your stuff grandpa
Hey move it you guys hurry
up don't let the straw
hat crew escape they're
the real perpetrators.
Fire! Fire!
Huh?
What is that?
It's time for Thunderbolt Disney!
Look at that!
He sent St.
Roswald slave free!
I don't know how he uncuffed
him, but stop that guy!
Captain John Bart.
Care to come along with me and my crew?
It's been a long time since
anyone's called me by that name.
According to you,
means I can be free from the celestial
dragons and leave this place?
Then I would be happy
to call you my captain.
I'm glad to hear it.
Half the things goes to Straw Hat, though.
We took out that bridge and
they're still chasing us.
Of course they are.
Probably some soldiers back in town, too.
We need to get the hell out of here.
Captain!
Captain K, are you okay?
Look up there.
Wait, is that...
What's he?
...doing out here.
That bear's a maniac.
How are we going to stop him?
What I want to know is,
how can a bear talk?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Are you shy about it?
We don't have time for this, Beppo.
Dammit!
They destroyed the bridge!
You're the new guy, so
you rank under me, okay?
As long as I'm not a slave, fine by me!
Captain! Look there! Huh?
Eustass...
and...
is that...?
Well, Tam, what's one of the
seven warlords doing here?
Trafalgar Law.
Would you look at that?
He knows my name.
Captain!
This archipelago is next to Navy
Headquarters and Marie's Wall.
Just about anybody can
show up here at any time.
Marine forces are coming up from the rear.
Really can't predict this guy.
Hey Trafalgar!
Don't get involved with this!
Would you give it up already?
You should know by now you
can't tell me what to do!
Anyway, big guy, we've had enough
ugly surprises for one day.
I'm not about to wait around
for an admiral to show up.
So I suggest you let us pass through.
Bartholomew Kuma?
Beethoven!
Boss, say something!
How dare they do this to you?
Damn those guys!
You know what?
I never expected Devil to be
so handsome under that mask.
Well, see ya.
Feel free to call us anytime.
We'll be there whenever you need us until
you're safely on your
way to Fishman Island.
Sounds good. Thanks, you guys.
Hey, ain't no thing, buddy.
Yeah, enough with the winking.
Oh, I forgot.
For you, Miss Mermaid.
Hey, you found my backpack.
Indeed.
That idiot Peterman had it.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Let's go, Rosie Life writers.
Yes, handsome Rosie.
They sure shot a bunch of weird stuff.
Probably trying to find
something that clicks.
Here we are. Let's hurry inside.
Sounds good.
We need to get Hachi to a bed.
Hey, Chaka, are you here? Open up.
Oh, it's Ray. Welcome back.
I wasn't expecting you.
Or rather, I wasn't expecting
them to find you so fast.
Hachi was seriously injured in the escape.
Do you have a bed?
That looks terrible. Hold on.
I'll throw something together for him.
You were on Gold Roger's crew!
I was.
In fact, I served as his vice-captain.
The name is Silvers Rayleigh.
It's nice to meet you.
Vice-captain!
Why didn't you tell them?
Slip your mind?
We only needed him to coat the
boat, so I didn't think about it.
Wait, you didn't know who he was?
Not his face, but I sure know his name!
He's in so many books, he's legendary!
It's definitely a name
everyone's heard at least once.
Gold Roger.
I seem to remember a rookie with that
name long ago, but I'm not sure, really.
So how do a big-shot pirate
and an octopus know each other?
Pachi rescued me.
I was stranded at sea and he found me.
That was over 20 years ago, but I'll
never forget it for as long as I live.
Pachi was still just a
little kid when it happened.
But he saved Rayleigh's life.
We remained good friends
after that incident
until he joined up with the Sun Pirates.
You ain't Arlong, right?
It's hard to believe.
I mean, Gold Roger was executed
22 years ago, wasn't he?
How did his vice-captain avoid
getting his head chopped off, too?
The Marines captured the
entire crew, didn't they?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, man.
The Marines didn't catch Roger.
See, the captain turned himself in.
The government made it sound
like they'd caught him, though.
Likely just to look tough,
rattling their sabers, if you will.
The king of the pirates turned himself in?
Because he saw the inevitable
end to our journey.
See, about four years before his
execution, Roger began to feel ill.
Turned out, he had
developed a fatal disease.
No matter how strong he was, the
illness he had was incurable.
He knew that he would
submit to it eventually.
But there was one man with the skill
and know-how to help ease his suffering.
A lighthouse keeper and
well-respected doctor.
A man residing at the Twin
Caves named Crocus. Huh?
We asked for his help and brought him on
as the ship's doctor for our final voyage.
Finally, three years later, while
managing to keep the disease at bay,
Roger achieved what was
said to be impossible.
He conquered the Grand Line.
Did you say Crocus?
At the Twin Capes?
Oh, that takes me back. Whoa!
That's crazy!
I thought the old man just lived
in the lighthouse for 50 years.
But he sailed with the
King of the Pirates.
Come to think of it, he did mention
being a ship's doctor for a while.
So he was a pirate on your
crew for those three years?
Oh, I have to assume you've met him then.
It's good to know that
he's alive and well.
Crocus agreed to join with us
because there was a certain
group of pirates he wanted to
search for on the Grand Line.
Brooke!
I bet he was talking about your crew!
Guess it's a small world after all!
Crocus, you sweet man!
You went to such lengths!
Yes, he was only a crew member
with us for those three years.
But we definitely considered
him one of our own.
It's been such a long time,
it'd be great to see him again.
So, what happened after
Roger conquered the sea?
That's when it all began.
The world started calling
Roger the king of the pirates.
Before that, no one had ever
called him the king of anything.
Honestly, titles don't hold much
meaning for a man about to die.
Still, Roger was overjoyed to hear it.
Whatever he did, he loved doing
it in a bold and flashy way.
Whether it was in battle or celebration,
he enjoyed living life to the fullest.
He seemed to take pleasure in thinking
out plans for the future as well,
even though he wouldn't be a part of it.
Eventually, as per Captain's orders, the
Roger Pirates were secretly disbanded.
One by one, everyone discreetly left
the crew and went their own way.
As comrades,
we risked our lives together,
but I know next to nothing about where
they are or what they're doing now.
Then about a year after we disbanded Roger
turned himself in and was incarcerated.
Shortly after it was announced that he
would be publicly executed in Log Town,
the settlement in the East
Blue where he was born
I've heard that many of
the young faces that bore
witness in the town square
that fateful day went
on to make names for
themselves on the high seas.
There was a silence that covered the
entire world the day of his execution.
I wasn't there in attendance myself.
But I hear that his final words
went a little something like this?
While they may execute me, I won't die.
The world government and the
Marines must have been shocked.
With one last remark from Roger,
the public execution
that was meant to serve
as an example into
warning to other pirates,
instead became the opening ceremony to
what would become the Great Pirate Era.
If anyone wants my treasure,
then it's yours for the taking.
Go find it!
I left everything I gathered in one place.
In seconds,
he changed the dim
flame of his life into a
raging hellfire that
spread across the world.
I never laughed as much,
nor have I cried as much,
nor drank as much as I did that night.
The captain was an amazing man.
He sure lived one hell of a life.
I'd heard it before but
it's still so amazing
when one of Roger's old
friends tells it it's.
Like it's a whole new
story wait it sounds like
you're trying to say that
Roger created the great.
Pirate era on purpose that
I couldn't tell you no
way to know for sure Roger
is no longer with us.
It's only the people who are living now
who can create and shape such an era.
I'm certain that there are people who
inherited that spirit of adventure from Roger.
That fateful day in the town square.
Your good friend Shanks
is probably one of them.
You know Shanks too, old man?
Perhaps you've heard of a pirate
named Buggy from the East Blue
Buggy?
He and shanks served us well.
They were both apprentices
on board roger's ship.
You mean Jake was on the
King of the Pirate ship?
I take it he never told you then.
I ran into him again, right here on
this archipelago about ten years ago.
I noticed he lost his trademark straw
hat, as well as losing his left arm.
When I asked him what happened,
he spoke about you with a smile.
I was shocked, Rayleigh.
I couldn't believe it.
In the East Blue, there's a kid who
said the same thing Captain Roger said.
His spirit lives on in him.
A Navy warship's been
spotted from the harbor!
Oh no, the Admiral's here!
Uh, this is Kizaru.
Uh, I've arrived on site.
Please respond. Over.